[
    {   
        "question": "All pensioneer loan must be??",
        "choice1": "Consumable",
        "choice2": "Validated",
        "choice3": "Consolidated",
        "choice4": "endorse from HR",
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "Customer is 60 years 11mnts, worked in KEBBI STATE PRIMARY SCHOOL STAFF PENSION BOARD (RETIREE) can he be granted for a fresh load",
        "choice1": "No is too old",
        "choice2": "Yes he/she can get loan",
        "choice3": "He/She will not pay back",
        "choice4": "Yes but he/she can get below #20,000",
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "__ and __ are one off fees paid at the beginning of the loan for the 90 days period",
        "choice1": "Availed Fee and Advisory Fee",
        "choice2": "Management Fee and Advisory Fee",
        "choice3": "Insurance Fee and Availed Fee",
        "choice4": "Upfront Fee and Management Fee",
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the maximum Rate for CAT A",
        "choice1": "29.95%",
        "choice2": "34%",
        "choice3": "31%",
        "choice4": "31.95%",
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the minimum loan amount for Loan Top Up",
        "choice1": "100,000",
        "choice2": "50,000",
        "choice3": "1000",
        "choice4": "10,000",
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "Which loan enables customer own and enjoy the benefits of brand new cars",
        "choice1": "Salary Loan",
        "choice2": "Auto Loan",
        "choice3": "Cash Loan",
        "choice4": "Fast Cash loan",
        "answer": 2
      },
    {
        "question": "A one month suspension of loan repayment is known as ?",
        "choice1": "Loan Maturity",
        "choice2": "Loan break",
        "choice3": "Payment Holiday",
        "choice4": "All of the above",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "CAT A below 100k without VCC the DBR is ?",
        "choice1": "50%",
        "choice2": "45%",
        "choice3": "33.3%",
        "choice4": "45% or 40%",
        "answer": 2
      },
    {
      "question": "Who is the head of Consumer underwriting?",
      "choice1": "Mr.Gbenga Adeyemi",
      "choice2": "Mrs.Mary Adelakun",
      "choice3": "Mr.Agbafo Franklin",
      "choice4": "Mr.Olayemi Ogunyankin",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Olayemi Johnson",
        "choice1": "Developer",
        "choice2": "Underwriter",
        "choice3": "Engineer",
        "choice4": "Pastor",
        "answer": 1
      }

   
  ]
  